<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<QuestDialog xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" huntingZoneId="15" id="4" voiceTypeId="0">
    <Text huntingZoneId="0" id="1" prevId="0" villagerId="0" />
    <Text huntingZoneId="216" id="100" prevId="0" villagerId="1028">
         
        <Page social="0">Jelena's plan got you into the manor. While Jelena cleared the way of alarms, you killed the vampir duke and duchess. You found the device that produced the dementaliths—and blew it to bits.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;A Scion priestess, Akia, vowed revenge for your meddling. By the time you killed her pet arachnen, she'd escaped, but you forged a new friendship with Jelena.</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="216" id="2" prevId="0" villagerId="1028">
         
        <Page social="4">The nobles use that teleportal to come and go unseen.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;They think it's safe because it's keyed to their blood. Thanks to you, we have some of that!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Everyone take a vial. See you on the other side!</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="488" id="3" prevId="2" villagerId="1001">
         
        <Page social="4">Shhh! They're right up those stairs!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Can you feel that tingling? Right in the back of your neck? That must be magic from their device. Blast, it's strong! We must be quick.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Okay, are we all in place?</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="488" id="4" prevId="3" villagerId="1001">
         
        <Page social="4">You'll be making a lot of noise, so I'll disable their alarms. We'll meet at the ladder to the ground floor.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;If anything gives you trouble, cut it down and let the Dream sort it out.</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="488" id="5" prevId="4" villagerId="1005">
         
        <Page social="4">You go crash {@LinkCreature:488#10#Duchess Tirania} and {@LinkCreature:488#13#Duke Volperon}'s little party.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I'll rig the temple door to open when they die. Then we can put an end to this mess.</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="15" id="6" villagerId="4">
         
        <Page social="0">All right. It's time to take out that device. Hum a song or count as high as you can—anything to keep your mind focused. Just make sure you destroy the target!</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="216" id="7" prevId="5" villagerId="1028">
         
        <Page social="4">Is this the end of Sinestral Manor?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We got rid of the duke and duchess and even destroyed the dementalith generator. All in a day's work, eh? Great job in there!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Now, maybe I can finally stretch out and take a breather. Yeah, right.</Page>
    
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
