<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<QuestDialog xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" huntingZoneId="56" id="2" voiceTypeId="0">
    <Text huntingZoneId="0" id="1" prevId="0" villagerId="0" />
    <Text huntingZoneId="256" id="100" prevId="0" villagerId="1010">
         
        <Page social="0">After ending the bloodletting at the Raven Altar, you went to Amena Quatla to end Thulsa's plan. You slew the sikandari priests and their argon reinforcements, giving Isrenia time to join with Sikander.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;But even as she did, Thulsa and Killian appeared. Sikander, maddened, erupted as Kelsaik.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;But Kaia assured you there was still hope. Thulsa couldn't control Kelsaik. Kaia ordered you to find an ancient artifact and destroy Kelsaik before Thulsa could bind it.</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="256" id="2" prevId="0" villagerId="1010">
         
        <Page social="0">The sikandaris live around Sikander's temple in Amena Quatla. Sikander rests in a massive golden egg, if the Vanguards aren't lying. Find Sonacria at Broken Bridge Camp. She'll know what to do now. And Kaia watch over you!</Page>
         
        <Page social="0" />
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="257" id="3" prevId="2" villagerId="1008">
         
        <Page social="4">&lt;PCNAME&gt;? I'd heard you were—&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Wait, what? The sikandaris are waking Sikander? Now?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Oh, blast and damnation! That explains all kinds of things.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;A huge parade of elders and attendants entered Sikander's temple this morning. Sikander sleeps in a huge egg down south, but I'd bet my weight in wine that ritual's in the temple!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Go! And may your strength suffice!</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="474" id="4" prevId="3" villagerId="1007">
         
        <Page social="4">Excellent work, &lt;PCNAME&gt;. Sikander's turmoil is lessening. He might heal on his own now...if left alone.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Isrenia, I sense you too! You know what you have to do, don't you—what Isren would want? And the cost?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;PCNAME&gt;, stop that ritual! If you don't, we're all done for. Even me. I can think of no flowery blessings—just know that I trust you with this.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Now go. Fight! Win!</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="474" id="5" prevId="4" villagerId="1008">
         
        <Page social="4">It's time. I'm ready.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;PCNAME&gt;...thank you. I enjoyed walking the mortal world for a little while with you.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;But now Sikander needs me...needs all I have.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Sikander! Remember Isren! Remember her—our—love for you!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Don't do this!</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="84" id="6" prevId="5" villagerId="1088">
         
        <Page social="4">You look pale &lt;PCNAME&gt;&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Please come in!</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="528" id="7" prevId="6" villagerId="5009">
         
        <Page social="4">Damn you, Thulsa! How can someone so smart be so stupid?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Be proud, mortal. Though Thulsa woke Kelsaik, through your efforts he lost control of it. Kelsaik is a crazed beast instead of an obedient weapon.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;This is a tragedy, and the beast is unimaginably dangerous, but we can beat them separately. Together they'd have been unstoppable.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Your mighty efforts, the lives of Kanmur and Isrenia? A high price. But you won us hope.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Can you stop him, Shieldmaiden?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
         
        <Page social="1">No.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Sikander is a god of my parents' generation. He may be beyond all our power, especially insane.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I can think of only one relic potent enough. Saleron, Killian and Icaruna's father, owns it—one of the great artifacts of the world's earliest days.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;But Killian and Thulsa will seek it, too.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Where's Saleron? Can I get there?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
         
        <Page social="0">Saleron is bound in a great cavern in Val Elenium. He won't give in to Thulsa or Killian willingly, but you must hurry.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Inform Tamur, then seek Fraya's aid.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Kelsaik is a raging, destructive force. Only Isrenia's influence keeps it from submitting to Thulsa. Kelsaik can lay waste to the world. In Thulsa's hands, that's exactly what it will do.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;There's greatness in you mortals. You show it. Thulsa fears it. Fight bravely, my friend. Win us the weapon we need.</Page>
    
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
