<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<QuestDialog xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" huntingZoneId="182" id="6" voiceTypeId="0">
    <Text huntingZoneId="0" id="1" prevId="0" villagerId="0" />
    <Text huntingZoneId="182" id="100" prevId="0" villagerId="2032">
         
        <Page social="0">Keezar, a Khirian shaman, was shrewd, but seemed out of her mind.&lt;BR&gt;Her ability was not reliable, but since she was the last hope to secure a working archdevan control pendant, there was no other choice but to trust her.</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="182" id="2" prevId="0" villagerId="2032">
         
        <Page social="1">How do I know what? Who are you? Did the archdevas send you?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;What's that you have there? A broken control pendant? How did you break this? They're meant to be indestructible and idiot-proof!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Oh, well, the damage is done. The only way to put this back together now would be some sort of super-powerful glue. "Power Glue," call it.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Uh, okay. Do you have such a glue?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
         
        <Page social="1">Well, no, &lt;PCNAME&gt;. I need the archdevas to think that these pendants cannot be repaired, once they're broken—otherwise they'll have no further use of me. But now that the Vanguard Initiative have finally arrived, there's no need for me to remain here.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;So, to make magical glue, you need magical horn. Say, the kind you'd find on devas. I'm sure you can find some of those.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"I have a good idea..."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="182" id="3" prevId="2" villagerId="2032">
         
        <Page social="1">Pretty, pretty horns! "A pointed projection of skin on the head of various animals consisting of a covering of keratin and other proteins surrounding a core of live bone." Ha! Bet you're wondering how I knew that, aren't you?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Is everyone here crazy?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="182" id="4" villagerId="2032">
         
        <Page social="0">One horn, two horn, red horn, war-torn.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Not enough, my foreign friend!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Two horn, once worn! More horn, less scorn!</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="182" id="5" prevId="3" villagerId="2032">
         
        <Page social="1">No need to get snippy, &lt;PCNAME&gt;. I have waited years in this awful place just to help you on your quest! But now that you're here, we can both go.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Let's talk outside, shall we?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"How do I get you out of here?" &lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
         
        <Page social="1">Click, click, double-quick! That's the wrong question! The right question is how do I get you out of here, when you're so slow?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"What? I'm not slow..."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="182" id="6" prevId="5" villagerId="2036">
         
        <Page social="1">How did you find me so soon? I won't go back! You can't make me!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Wait...oh, you're still the same one. What was your name? What was your quest? Have I already asked you about your favorite color?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"I need this pendant repaired. Remember?"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
         
        <Page social="1">A broken control pendant? How did you break this? They're meant to be indestructible and idiot-proof!&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"We've already had this conversation!"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
         
        <Page social="1">I cannot teach this one. No patience.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Fine. Glue you want. Glue you shall have.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"Finally!"&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
    
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
