<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<QuestDialog xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" huntingZoneId="13" id="11" voiceTypeId="0">
    <Text huntingZoneId="0" id="1" prevId="0" villagerId="0" />
    <Text huntingZoneId="0" id="100" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
         
        <Page social="0">You were ordered to redeploy to the Tainted Gorge to go on the offensive. En route, you came across a crashed courier named Chione, who asked you to deliver some orders for her. You delivered the orders to Riel and prepared for the next stage.</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="0" id="2" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
         
        <Page social="4">I think Elleon may have gone on to explore the Tainted Gorge. If he's not there, we could probably still find a clue as to what he's looking for.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Get further instructions from Adria.</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="64" id="3" prevId="2" villagerId="1001">
         
        <Page social="4">Okay, I want you to head over to the Tainted Gorge. There'll be some kind of clue out there, I'm sure.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Redeploying some of our troops to the Tainted Gorge is probably a good idea, anyway. We keep trying to pull out, but somehow the threat out there never dies down.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Talk to Bipi first, though. She needs some help.</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="64" id="4" prevId="3" villagerId="1033">
         
        <Page social="4">That flighty silly girl!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I do need help, thank you. Chione's airship crashed en route to the Tainted Gorge. She was carrying vital supplies and Leander's report, but she couldn't fight her way out of a pillow fort.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Head east from the Tower Base and link up with her.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Time is of the essence.</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="213" id="5" prevId="4" villagerId="1007">
         
        <Page social="4">The report? Oh yes, it's safe and sealed!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Edan's supposed to read it. I've got a bit of a mess here though, so I can't take it onward.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Perhaps you could!</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="213" id="6" prevId="5" villagerId="1134">
         
        <Page social="4">Leander's report, eh? Let's take a look....&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Demons, as we suspected—though we didn't dream they'd be this powerful. The Tainted Gorge is crawling with our enemies, but they're not fighting us. They're looking for something.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Whatever it is, we'd best get to it before they do!</Page>
    
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
