<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<QuestDialog xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" huntingZoneId="13" id="31" voiceTypeId="0">
    <Text huntingZoneId="0" id="1" prevId="0" villagerId="0" />
    <Text huntingZoneId="64" id="100" prevId="0" villagerId="1006">
         
        <Page social="0" />
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="64" id="2" prevId="0" villagerId="1006">
         
        <Page social="4">I've got another task for you. It's important, but not critical. East of here there's a rock outcropping with a terrace about halfway up. Ramun mentioned some activity around our detector stone there. If you could check the area out, I'd appreciate it.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;On a personal note, I understand there's not only a really amazing view of our camp from up there, but also a spectacular &lt;b&gt;skyreach flower&lt;/b&gt; that blooms once a day under the arch.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Climb up the &lt;b&gt;vines&lt;/b&gt; and take a look around. Please pick me one of those flowers, and use this &lt;b&gt;teleport scroll&lt;/b&gt; to return.</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="213" id="3" prevId="2" villagerId="1053">
         
        <Page social="4">(It looks like the detector stone Jorhon was speaking of, placed here to detect any intruders that may wander near Mathar Spire.)&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;(Now, climb the vine to the top of the spire.)</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="64" id="4" prevId="3" villagerId="1001">
         
        <Page social="4">Scratches on the stone? Very interesting. Didn't think that was possible. I'll have another patrol added to the area.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;And what's that you've got there?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"A skyreach flower..."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
         
        <Page social="0">Another flower? I don't mind the attention, but I've got more on my mind than sweet-smelling blossoms right now. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We depend on those markers to keep our camp safe—if someone—or some thing—is investigating them, we need to be on alert.</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="64" id="5" villagerId="1001">
         
        <Page social="0">Anything to report?</Page>
    
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
