<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<QuestDialog xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" huntingZoneId="8" id="3" voiceTypeId="0">
    <Text huntingZoneId="0" id="1" prevId="0" villagerId="0" />
    <Text huntingZoneId="208" id="100" prevId="0" villagerId="1001">
         
        <Page social="0">The gulas of the Hungry Caverns are abducting people for their stewpots.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;One of the abductees, Hennika, was the younger sister of Detrian—an acquaintance of yours. Detrian went into the Hungry Caverns after her.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You never found Detrian, but you did recover his sword from a gula. You rescued Hennika from a slave market, and she swore on her brother's sword that she would avenge him.</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="208" id="2" prevId="0" villagerId="1001">
         
        <Page social="5">Okay, this has to stop—the gulas are out of control!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I have a list here of the most recent people they've carried off for their stewpots. Go into the Hungry Caverns and rescue as many as you can.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;What? Is there a name you recognize?</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="208" id="3" prevId="2" villagerId="1001">
         
        <Page social="5">Yes, that's Detrian's sister, Hennika. He already went in after her, so you might as well add him to the list.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Search Vanguard Post Alpha in the Cavern of Shackles. If you hurry you might save a few of them from being eaten.</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="208" id="4" prevId="3" villagerId="1022">
         
        <Page social="5">Who goes there? Wait...you're not Detrian!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;What? Detrian went into the caverns? He hasn't got a chance in there!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Okay, I can see you're going to follow him in, so here's what you have to know. The kitchens are on this level. That's where they'll put prisoners before...you know.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Don't wind up in the pot yourself, &lt;PCCLASS:lcase&gt;!</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="208" id="5" prevId="4" villagerId="1031">
         
        <Page social="5">(The bite marks on this corpse look gula-sized. It's been dead a long time, so it's not a recent prisoner.)</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="208" id="6" prevId="5" villagerId="1022">
         
        <Page social="5">They weren't there? Then they must be in the lower levels.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We're still racing against time. Check in at Vanguard Post Beta. Ask for Rendia. If anyone's heard something new, she'll know about it.</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="208" id="7" prevId="6" villagerId="1014">
         
        <Page social="5">Yes, Loxetrius's instincts are as sharp as ever. The abductees, and maybe Detrian, are almost certainly in the prison cells—an area the gulas call the Cavern of Tears.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;There are two cell blocks. The {@LinkCreature:208#1024#first cell block} is straight down the passage.</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="208" id="8" prevId="7" villagerId="1024">
         
        <Page social="5">&lt;PCNAME&gt;...(cough)...(gasp). I tried...&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I could see Hennika, but there were too many of them. I couldn't get to her.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The {@LinkCreature:8#4011#aberrant gulons} took her to the &lt;FONT COLOR='#0080FF'&gt;&lt;A href="markmap:loc=7004#78829,63010,-3794&amp;type=1&amp;name=second cell block"&gt;second cell block&lt;/A&gt;&lt;/FONT&gt;. We have to save her, &lt;PCNAME&gt;...&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"We will."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
         
        <Page social="4">I just can't...move right now, &lt;PCNAME&gt;.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I should rest...&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Just for a minute...&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;(Detrian stops breathing, and you can't find a pulse. His eyes remain open, as if still looking for his sister.)</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="208" id="9" prevId="8" villagerId="1027">
         
        <Page social="5">Fates be damned, I'm glad to see you! I thought it was the stewpot for sure!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Are you in the same unit as that young soldier who found us? He fought so bravely...</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="208" id="10" prevId="8" villagerId="1028">
         
        <Page social="5">Thank you for saving me! What's your name? I'm naming my firstborn child after you!</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="208" id="11" prevId="8" villagerId="1029">
         
        <Page social="5">We're scared and weak, but otherwise fine.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Can't say the same for that soldier who tried to rescue us...&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Did he make it out okay?</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="208" id="12" prevId="8" villagerId="1005">
         
        <Page social="5">Hennika...I feel so sorry for her.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;That soldier who tried to rescue us was her brother.</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="208" id="13" prevId="8" villagerId="1026">
         
        <Page social="5">I thought I was going to end my life in a gula frying pan, that's for sure.</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="208" id="14" prevId="9" villagerId="1025">
         
        <Page social="5">&lt;PCNAME&gt;! I remember you! Where's Detrian? Is he?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Don't say it! Don't!&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"His last thought was of you..."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
         
        <Page social="5">Oh, Detrian...Detrian...(sob)...&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I know he'd want me to be brave, but it's not easy.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;And he'd want you to avenge him, &lt;PCNAME&gt;.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;The last sight I had was of him fighting one of those {@LinkCreature:8#4051#vulgar inquisitors}.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;"That's my target, then."&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
         
        <Page social="0">I can't keep crying like this. I have to be strong for the other survivors.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I'll get everyone up to Avenger Outpost.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Look for my brother's sword. That's how you'll know which inquisitor to kill.</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="208" id="15" prevId="14" villagerId="1030">
         
        <Page social="5">Detrian's sword...&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Detrian, if you're listening, I swear upon this sword that I'll become a Kaia's Sword like you, and rescue people in your name.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;This I swear!</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="208" id="16" villagerId="1030">
         
        <Page social="0">Avenge Detrian! Kill the inquisitor and bring back my brother's sword!</Page>
    
    </Text>
    <Text huntingZoneId="208" id="17" prevId="15" villagerId="1001">
         
        <Page social="5">The survivors made it back here, &lt;PCNAME&gt;. Well done!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I was so sorry to hear about Detrian. He was a good soldier. Perhaps we'll see him in our dreams.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I'd like that. And I think Detrian's sister would, too. Such a serious little girl...</Page>
    
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
