<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" id="99" huntingZoneId="10" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0" />
    <Text id="100" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">Alptinus put an end to a destructive faction war over a cache of ancient relics by instituting the Cursus Honorum, a code of conduct by which guilds could share in their use. Using the relics, he created a floating castle out of a ruined temple, and used this base to enforce his code for many years.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Gruber, a supposedly reformed criminal, betrayed Alptinus and Lightkeepers, stole one of the relics, and kidnapped a Mysterium researcher.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Working as a deputized Lightkeeper, &lt;PCNAME&gt; defeated Gruber and rescued the researcher, earning a place in the sky.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0">
        <Page social="0">Greetings, &lt;PCNAME&gt;.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I am Lightkeeper Sharn, and word of your deeds and commitment to justice has reached us through mutual acquaintances.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;There is a matter I wish to discuss with you, if you have time to meet with myself and our leader, Alptinus.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Mention my name to Lukan, Castanica's flight manager, and he'll assist you further.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;It is a manner of some urgency, but I'll understand if you are too busy to help.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3" huntingZoneId="61" prevId="2" villagerId="1008">
        <Page social="0">&lt;PCNAME&gt;! I was wondering if you were among those invited! Lightkeeper Sharn said the best of the best were coming to see him, and you're the first to arrive.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Are you ready to travel to Nakatam Tower?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;What's this about?&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">The Lightkeepers' fortress is...hard to get to. Not many flight managers know the way there, but I'm happy to help. Sharn said it was important, and if someone like you was invited...&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Let's just say it's a flight like no other. Are you ready?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;I'm ready.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Okay. Hang on tight!</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4" huntingZoneId="210" prevId="3" villagerId="3001">
        <Page social="0">&lt;PCNAME&gt;, I'm so glad you've come. I am Lightkeeper Sharn, and I hope you can solve our problem.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Our order is a proud one, so it's not easy for us to ask for help like this. Our leader, Alptinus, will fill you in on exactly what we need, but I wanted to tell you about the order itself before I hand you off to him.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Our story is really the story of Nakatam Tower, so I should probably start there. This place was once an abandoned temple complex, which contained a cache of powerful relics. Do you have a few minutes to hear about it?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Wouldn't be here if I wasn't interested.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Many factions converged on the site, hoping to seize the relics. But not everyone came to conquer. The Mysterium sent a team of researchers, including Alptinus' daughter Elie.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;When Elie was injured during a battle between competing guilds, Alptinus knew that the world needed more responsible leadership, and our order was formed.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We took control of the temple, and Elie used the relics to float it. We then built Nakatam Tower on its foundation, and instituted the Cursus Honorum as a way to regulate who had access.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;But that's Alptinus' story to tell. You can usually find him at one of the observation posts.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5" huntingZoneId="210" prevId="4" villagerId="3002">
        <Page social="0">Ah, &lt;PCNAME&gt;. I am honored you accepted our invitation.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I saw you talking to Sharn, so I'm assuming he filled you in on the history of our order. It's that history that led to our current situation, so I'm hoping you can help us fix one of our mistakes.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;I'm happy to help.&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Good, good. When I instituted the Cursus Honorum, my hope was that guild leaders would police their organizations and adhere to a higher ethical standard. But there are always those who take joy from the grief they cause others, and the Lightkeepers exist to stop them.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Until yesterday, one of our greatest successes was reforming the bandit lord Gruber. He became a trusted member of our order, but we now know it was all part of a larger plan. Instead of forswearing his gang of thieves, he's been secretly rebuilding them, waiting for a chance to strike.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;What do you mean?&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Yesterday, Gruber and his men attacked a team of Lightkeepers and stole a relic we'd entrusted to the Mysterium, along with the research team they were escorting. I'm not exactly sure what his plan is, but Gruber's betrayal could herald the start of another faction war, and we need to put an end to it, and him, as soon as possible.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Normally we'd take care of this ourselves, but our forces are spread pretty thin right now, and we're not sure who we can trust. This is why we need people like yourself, who are recommended by the gods themselves.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Sharn will give you more details on your mission, but for now consider yourself deputized.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="6" huntingZoneId="210" prevId="5" villagerId="3001">
        <Page social="0">Welcome back, Lightkeeper. Your mission is a simple one. The relic Gruber and his gang stole is one of the ones that keeps Nakatam Tower afloat. We believe he intends to crash us if he can, but I have no idea how he plans to do that.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Where is Gruber?&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">If he's looking to bring us down, he can't have gone far. I suspect he's holed up in the Boan Strand, one of his old hideouts.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;It's vital that you defeat Gruber, recover the relic, and rescue the kidnapped researcher. Preferably in that order, but I'll leave the specifics to you. &lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Sounds easy enough. Anything else?&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Remember &lt;PCNAME&gt;, you're a Lightkeeper now. Both our allies and enemies will expect certain behavior from you, and I trust that you'll act accordingly. But it's far more important that we head off another faction war than look good, so do whatever you have to do to get the job done.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I'll have one of our people send you to Viper Camp, and leave the rest in your capable hands.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="7" huntingZoneId="210" prevId="6" villagerId="3004">
        <Page social="0">A Lightkeeper. Of course.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You're too late, hero. I've unlocked the relic's secrets.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Put the relic down, Gruber!&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">You fool. You're just like the rest of them. Narrow. Limited.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I used the relic to transform myself... there's no going back now.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;This power… I... will live... forever...</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="8" huntingZoneId="210" prevId="7" villagerId="3003">
        <Page social="0">A Lightkeeper?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I'm saved, I am saved!&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;Are you alright?&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">I am now. At first I thought Gruber was just a thief, but then he moved up to kidnapping.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;He wanted to use my research to do something crazy, but the Mysterium never negotiates with bandits. Besides, his plan was insane. Who thinks something like that would ever work?&lt;BR&gt;</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="9" huntingZoneId="10" villagerId="99">
        <Page social="0">Listen, there's still some of Gruber's men hanging around here. If you can clear a path for me, I'll head back to Viper Camp on my own.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Once we're out of danger, I can send you back to Nakatam Tower.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="10" huntingZoneId="210" prevId="8" villagerId="3001">
        <Page social="0">&lt;PCNAME&gt;! I knew you could do this. Thank you so much.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Gruber's betrayal will haunt the Lightkeepers for some time, but with the assistance of heroes like you, we'll rebuild the order in no time.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;What happens now?&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Well, for starters, you're no longer a deputy Lightkeeper. You've more than earned a place among us, if you want one. Alptinus will handle your formal induction himself.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Long term, we're going to rethink a few of our precepts, maybe share a few of our secrets so that things like this don't happen again. If there were a few more floating guild halls, maybe the temptation to steal relics wouldn't be as strong.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;We've already changed our passwords and secret handshakes, hopefully that will be enough to prevent another betrayal.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="11" huntingZoneId="210" prevId="10" villagerId="3002">
        <Page social="0">I'm glad you were able to help us out, &lt;PCNAME&gt;. No one wants to see another faction war. &lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Are you ready to officially join our ranks?&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;What will that entail?&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Bandits like Gruber will always threaten the peace, and our hope is that heroes like you will always be there to stop them. As a Lightkeeper, all you have to do is keep fighting for what you believe is right, no more, no less. We trust that you'll act responsibly.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;So from this day forward, Lightkeeper, you will always have a place here in Nakatam Tower.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
