<QuestDialog xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog QuestDialog.xsd" id="69" huntingZoneId="3" voiceTypeId="0" xmlns="https://vezel.dev/novadrop/dc/QuestDialog">
    <Text id="1" huntingZoneId="0" prevId="0" villagerId="0" />
    <Text id="100" huntingZoneId="59" prevId="0" villagerId="1031">
        <Page social="0">Quest "Avatar Weapon"</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="2" huntingZoneId="59" prevId="0" villagerId="1031">
        <Page social="0">Rumor has it that Roson - a master trapper from Crescentia - recently found an ancient relic with magical power.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;However, no one knows the details. And what does that mean? That without any evidence, you shouldn't throw around phrases like "magical relic"!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;So, you need to find out the truth. Talk to Roson and find out what this relic story is all about.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="3" huntingZoneId="59" prevId="2" villagerId="1031">
        <Page social="0">What? They say I have a magical relic? That's just ridiculous!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;It always happens: people start gossiping without knowing the details and pass on rumors without bothering to verify them.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;In reality, I only know the area where parts of the relic can be found. And one part alone has no value. You'll need to collect a bunch of them.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&amp;quot;But... for what?&amp;quot;&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Recently, I heard a legend about relics of the ancient gods.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;If you gather all parts of such a relic and restore it, you can create an amazing weapon that gains divine power! The avatar weapon.&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&amp;quot;Sounds like... cheap nonsense.&amp;quot;&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Yes, I know. But all my research leads to this. That's why I'm hunting relics - I want to test my theory and see if it's true or false.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;But finding them is really hard for me. I was never a good fighter, and the relic parts, unfortunately, are almost always found with monsters attracted by the energy they emit. I'm a researcher, you see...&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;But you, you're an experienced fighter, right? Maybe you... well... you know what I'm talking about? And you'll show me what you manage to find, won't you?</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="4" huntingZoneId="59" prevId="3" villagerId="1031">
        <Page social="0">Did you manage to find anything? So it's true?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Could my theory be confirmed? I must know!&lt;NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;&amp;quot;Here, take a look.&amp;quot;&lt;/NEXTPAGEBUTTON&gt;</Page>
        <Page social="0">Oh, gods!.. This is incredible! What a magnificent greatsword... any adventurer's dream!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;You've managed to confirm my theory! Thank you!&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;As a token of gratitude, I want to give this sword to you. In your hands, this weapon will be of greater use.&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;I believe there are other relics on the continent. I bet it won't be difficult for you to find them. Don't stop searching! And good luck on your future journeys.</Page>
    </Text>
    <Text id="5" huntingZoneId="59" villagerId="1031">
        <Page social="0">Oh, no! You couldn't find them? Could my theory be wrong?&lt;BR&gt;&lt;BR&gt;Please, keep searching! I really want to find proof that I'm right.</Page>
    </Text>
</QuestDialog>
